RG 005:029, Office of the Governor: Raymond E. Baldwin (1943-1946)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Subject Files, 1946-10
  - War Council - Maternal Care (Box 480)
  - War Council - Medical and Public Health (Box 480)
  - War Council - Membership (Box 480)
  - War Council - Notification of Meetings and Minutes of (Box 481)
  - War Council - Nurses (Box 481)
  - War Council - Nutrition (Box 481)
  - War Council - Organization Chart (Box 481)
  - War Council - Pediatric Advisory Committee (Box 481)
  - War Council - Plant and Mercantile Protection (Box 481)
  - War Council - Police (Box 481)
  - War Council - Progress Reports (Box 481)
  - War Council - Protection of Crippled and Invalid People, Committee on (Box 481)
  - War Council - Protective (Box 481)
  - War Council - Publications (Box 481)
  - War Council - Public Relations (Box 481)
  - War Council - Recommendations, 3 folders (Box 481)
  - War Council - Reconversion Meeting Re: Agriculture, 1945 September 10 (Box 481)
  - War Council - Reconversion Meeting, State Armory Officers Lounge, 1945 April 24 (Box 481)
  - War Council - Reconversion Meeting, Hartford Club, 1945 August 23 (Box 481)
  - War Council - Reconversion Program, 2 folders (Box 481)
  - War Council - Recreation (Box 481)
  - War Council - Recruiting and Training (Box 481)
  - War Council - Releases (Box 481)
  - War Council - Reports (Box 481)
  - War Council - Reports concerning Discontinuance and Reorganization of the Conn. War Council (Box 481)
  - War Council - Resignations (Box 481)
  - War Council - Responses to Letters from Governor and WPB Re: Sticking to War Jobs (Box 482)
  - War Council - Salvage (Box 482)
  - War Council - Servicemen and Women, Reception to Returning (Box 482)
  - War Council - Small Business and Business Enterprise (Box 482)
  - War Council - Social Protection (Box 482)
  - War Council - Social Service and Welfare (Box 482)
  - War Council - Speeches (Box 482)
  - War Council - Staff (Box 482)
  - War Council - Suggestions Received (Box 482)
  - War Council - Surgical Advisory Committee (Box 482)
  - War Council - Theaters (Box 482)
  - War Council - Training (Box 482)
  - War Council - Transportation (Box 482)
  - War Council - V-Day (Box 482)
  - War Council - Victory Manpower, 2 folders (Box 482)
  - War Council - Victory Manpower Com[mission], Letters to Local War Councils (Box 482)
  - War Council - Victory Manpower Committee - Publicity (Box 482)
  - War Council - Victory Manpower Comm[ittee] - Seniority (Box 482)
  - War Council - War Gardens (Box 482)
  - War Council - War Industries (Box 482)
  - War Council - Water Protection (Box 482)
  - War Council - Wholesale and Retail Business (Box 482)
  - War Council - Women's Division (Box 482)
  - War Council - Youth Council (Box 482)
  - War Department (Box 482)
  - War Finance Committee (Box 482)
  - War Food Administration - Davis (Box 482)
  - War Fund (Box 482)
  - War Gardens (Box 482)
  - War Industries Commission (Box 483)
  - War Industries, Small (Box 483)
  - War Labor Board (Box 483)
  - War Loan Drive (Box 483)
  - War Manpower Commission - Bridgeport Victory Luncheon, 1945 March 14 (Box 483)
  - War Manpower Commission - McNutt (Box 483)
  - War Orders [5 folders] (Box 483)
  - War Plants, Governor's trips to (Box 483)
  - War Powers (Box 483)
  - War Production Board (Box 483)
  - War Savings (Box 484)
  - War Wives' Letters (Box 484)
  - Warner Brothers (Box 484)
  - Water Commission, Channel Enlargement - Norwich (Box 484)
  - Water Commission, Mansfield Hollow Dam (Box 484)
  - Watertown Cooperative Association (Box 484)
  - Welfare, Child (Box 484)
  - Welfare, Child, Deputy Commissioner of (Box 484)
  - Welfare Department (Box 484)
  - Women's Army Auxiliary Corps (Box 484)
  - Women's Army Corps (Box 484)
  - Workmen's Compensation Commissioners (Box 484)
  - W[orks] P[rogress] A[dministration] (Box 484)
  - Yale and Town Strike (Box 484)
  - Miscellaneous and Unfiled Material (Box 485)
    Unarranged.
    - Misc. Correspondence Re: F[air] E[mployment] P[ractices] Bill Leg. (Box 485)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence In Reference to Legislation of Bills, 1945 (Box 485)
    - Christmas Message By Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Connecticut Forum - WTHD Recording, 1945 December 24 (Box 485)
    - Final Message to the Legislature By Governor Raymond E. Baldwin, 1945 June 6 (Box 485)
    - Governor's Message to General Assembly, 1946 May 7 (Box 485)
    - Governor's Message to the Honorable Members of the Senate and House of Representatives, 1945 (Box 485)
    - Governor's Office Governor's Residence (Box 485)
    - Governor's Statements to the Connecticut General Assembly (Box 485)
    - Excerpts from Governor Baldwin's Inaugural Address, 1945 January 3 (Box 485)
    - Governor's Contingent Fund (Box 485)
    - Governors, Correspondence with (Box 485)
    - Governor's Letters About Book, Decentralize for Liberty (Box 485)
    - Special Message to Special Session of the General Assembly - "Mental Hospital Conditions", 1946 May (Box 485)
    - House Bills HB -2900 - HB - 3099 (Box 485)
- Series 3. War Orders, 1944-1946; 2002-019
  - War order terminating An Act Concerning a Food Emergency, 1945 September 21 (Box 1)
  - Complete set of engrossed and gold seal war orders, 1944-1946; 2 folders (Box 1)
- Series 4. Committee to Study the Medical and Hospital Service at Connecticut Veterans Home and Hospital, 1946; 2002-067
  - Report, 1946
    In shared hollinger box.